(Penny:)on a cheap monkey movie
(Penny:)all because some dumb girl
thought it was beneath her.
(Leonard:)At least they talked
about you on Letterman.
(Leonard:)Come on, I can drive you
wherever you need to go.
(Penny:)How?
Unlike me, you have a job.
(Penny:)I'm just gonna have to go back
to being a waitress.
(Penny:)Like I will be
for the rest of my life.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, would you wrap it up?
We're waiting on you.
(Penny:)I'm sorry, is the fact
that my life's falling apart
(Penny:)interfering with your board game?
(Sheldon:)It is.
(Sheldon:)You were wrong, friend Howard.
She completely understood.
(Raj:)Hey, you busy?
(Amy:)No. What's up?
(Raj:)Have you heard back from Emily?
(Sheldon:)I have.
Great! And?
(Amy:)And I'm afraid she doesn't think
you're right for her.
(Raj:)I give you one simple thing to do.
(Raj:)Contact a complete stranger and
make her fall in love with me,
and you blow it!